<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Admin</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="username">username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">login</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Wrong Password!!!</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="start">Start NavigationDrawer</string>
    <string name="close">Close NavigationDrawer</string>
    <string name="history">Rajshahi University of Engineering and Technology (RUET) is the 2nd oldest prestigious public Engineering University of Bangladesh offers quality education and research in the field of engineering and technology. The university established in 1964 as Rajshahi Engineering College with three Engineering departments namely Mechanical Engineering, Electrical and Electronic Engineering and Civil Engineering. The institute started with Bachelor degree program and limited number of students (122) enrolled in three departments each year. Later it was converted to Bangladesh Institute of Technology (BIT), Rajshahi in 1986 to enhance the technical education. The institute is upgraded as Rajshahi University of Engineering and Technology (RUET) in September, 2003 to enhance the technical education and research. The university is financed by the Government through the university Grants Commission of Bangladesh. The university is an autonomous statutory organization of the Government of Bangladesh functioning within the "Rajshahi University of Engineering and   Technology Act 2003. Currently, the university comprises 14 departments including engineering and sciences offers under–graduate and post–graduate degrees. Every year 725 most brilliant students are enrolled for the undergraduate program (session 2014–2015) through transparent and standard admission test. About 3000 students are pursuing their higher study in this green campus including under-graduate and post-graduate with over 200 prominent faculty members of diverse field of expertise. In graduate level, M.Sc. Engg., M. Engg., M.Phil and PhD programs and research are continuing in a qualitative manner under the faculties. The university also receive a significant numbers of international students are continuing their higher study in this campus. The medium of instruction and necessary assessment of this university is English.</string>
    <string name="overview"><![CDATA[Rajshahi University of Engineering & Technology (RUET) is the prestigious public Engineering University & center of excellence offers high quality education and research in the field of engineering and technology. RUET is well balanced urban and natural environment and convenience. Rapid globalization, industrialization, presence of problems, depletion of natural resources, environmental damage, world financial insecurity, poverty, etc are the global challenge for human being as a whole. Handling such global issues require wide range of quality people share their knowledge to cooperate and take action. RUET is the center of excellence to cultivate such talented individuals who take the lead of such issues sharing their technical knowledge and experience is the most important duty of this university. RUET not only serve for the expectation of public but also contribute to human society as a whole.The university comprises engineering and sciences departments’ offers under-graduate and post-graduate degrees. Every year most brilliant students are enrolled for the undergraduate program through transparent and standard admission test. About 3000 students are pursuing their higher study in this green campus including under-graduate and post-graduate with over 200 prominent faculty members of diverse field of expertise. The university also receive a significant numbers of international students are continuing their higher study in this campus.The faculty members and students (UG & PG) of this university engaged with qualitative research work in a multiple research fields and well equipped modern laboratory environment. The faculty members invest their most of the time in research activities jointly with foreign faculties beyond their regular academic duties. Every year the university received exiting number of research paper published by the students and faculty members in the world class high impact factor peer reviewed international journal.The graduates from this university is well enough to cope any challenge in the field of engineering, technology, research, leadership, management, etc on demand of national and global needs. Many of the students and faculty members receive full funded international scholarship for their higher study and appoint in world top rank universities as a quality faculty members and researchers upon completion the degree. RUET is committed to continue the progress and contributes on national and global development]]></string>
    <string name="campus_details">Rajshahi University of Engineering and Technology (RUET) is situated in the northern part of Bangladesh name Rajshahi is one of the largest divisional headquarter of the country.  The campus is located about 250 km north-west of Dhaka city and in urban area of Rajshahi adjoining with Dhaka-Rajshahi highway nearby of Rajshahi University. Dhaka to Rajshahi can be reached in about 5 hours by car, 6 hours by public bus, 6.5 hours by inter-city train and half an hour’s by airlines. The university is about 10 minutes drive (4 km) from the railway station and bus terminal and 20 minutes drive (8 km) from the Shah Makhdum Airport Rajshahi. Auto rickshaw, CNG and public bus is available 24 hours to reach the university from all the terminals.</string>
    <string name="CSE">Computer Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="EEE">Electrical and Electronic Engineering</string>
    <string name="ECE">Electrical and Computer Engineering</string>
    <string name="ETE">Electronic and Telecommunication Engineering</string>
    <string name="Civil">Civil Engineering</string>
    <string name="Mechanical">Mechanical Engineering</string>
    <string name="IPE">Industrial and Production Engineering</string>
    <string name="architecture">Architecture</string>
    <string name="Motivation_Speech">Heaven\'s Light is Our Guide</string>
</resources>